[
    {
        "question": "In what sea will you find the island group known as the Cyclades?",
        "answer": "Aegean Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Namibia formerly called?",
        "answer": "South-West Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Canadian city of Windsor is linked to what US city by the Ambassador Bridge?",
        "answer": "Detroit"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Shenandoah Valley is located in which eastern US state?",
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two lakes meet at the Straits of Mackinac?",
        "answer": "Lake Michigan and Lake Huron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows through the city of Savannah?",
        "answer": "Savannah River"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what time zone is Oklahoma located?",
        "answer": "Central Time Zone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tunisia is part of which continent?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sea borders Tunisia to the north?",
        "answer": "Mediterranean sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital city of American Samoa, a group of islands in the South Pacific?",
        "answer": "Pago pago"
    },
    {
        "question": "Avarua, the capital of the Cook Islands, is located on which South Pacific atoll?",
        "answer": "Rarotonga"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has Cayenne as its capital?",
        "answer": "French Guiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country formerly ruled Iceland?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gulf of Bothnia is considered to be part of which continent?",
        "answer": "Europe"
    },
    {
        "question": "Trout Creek is located in which U.S state?",
        "answer": "Montana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two countries make up the island of Hispaniola?",
        "answer": "Haiti and The Dominican Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fourth largest Portugese-speaking country in the world?",
        "answer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second largest African country that also has the shortest coastline?",
        "answer": "Democratic Republic of the Congo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the red circle on the Japanese flag represent?",
        "answer": "The Sun"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2022, this city was named by Cond\u00e9 Nast `The best big city in the U.S.` for the 6th year in a row.",
        "answer": "Chicago, Illinois"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US territory of Puerto Rico?",
        "answer": "San Juan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Oregon?",
        "answer": "Salem"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Chocolate Mountains are located in what desert?",
        "answer": "Sonoran Desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river was dammed to create Lake Chickamauga?",
        "answer": "Tennessee River"
    },
    {
        "question": "The mouth of what bay is located between Cape Charles and Cape Henry?",
        "answer": "Chesapeake Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Alabama?",
        "answer": "Montgomery"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paakantyi is spoken by which group of people?",
        "answer": "Australian Aboriginal people -- Also spelled Paakantji, Barkindji and Barkandji, it is a nearly extinct language spoken along the Darling River in New South Wales."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal are the Canary Islands named after?",
        "answer": "Dog -- Canariae is Latin for dog. According to the historian Pliny the Elder, the island Canaria contained `vast multitudes of dogs of very large size.`"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Ecuador and Bolivia?",
        "answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Morocco and Tunisia?",
        "answer": "Algeria"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many territories are there in Canada?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the names of the Canadian territories?",
        "answer": "Northwest Territories, Yukon and Nunavut"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Bermuda Triangle is located in what ocean?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state would you find Glacier National Park?",
        "answer": "Montana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Pentagon building physically located?",
        "answer": "Arlington, Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Grenada is part of which continent?",
        "answer": "North America"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mus\u00e9e d`Orsay in Paris was originally what?",
        "answer": "Railway Station"
    },
    {
        "question": "Devils Tower is located in what US state?",
        "answer": "Wyoming"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state would you find Devils Tower?",
        "answer": "Wyoming"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a native of Tangier called?",
        "answer": "Tangerian"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Plains of Abraham is in which Canadian province?",
        "answer": "Quebec"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country`s flag features the phrase `Order and Progress`?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the suffix \u201c-stan\u201d mean?",
        "answer": "`Place of`"
    },
    {
        "question": "What state is home to the Crazy Horse Memorial?",
        "answer": "South Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lowest natural point on Earth?",
        "answer": "The Challenger Deep"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s late monarch, King Bhumibol Adulyadej, got a patent for a rainmaking technology?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country, other than Switzerland, uses the Swiss franc?",
        "answer": "Liechtenstein"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Luxembourg?",
        "answer": "Luxembourg City"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is Cusco located?",
        "answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Minnesota?",
        "answer": "Saint Paul"
    }
]